{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"9.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":3676,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":8,"width":1842,"height":952,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si1702","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5210","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_1","title":"Using Grouping and Masking ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5182","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1702","si5210"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5182"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1","title":"Grouping lets you rotate, flip, move, or resize all shapes or objects at the same time as though they were a single shape or object. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5227","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":138},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5227"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"A masking image is a method used to hide some portions of an image and to open some portions. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5281","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_2"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":165},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5281"}}},{"id":"Slide5245","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":2923},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5245"}}},{"id":"si5292","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5282q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5403","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5399","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5319","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5326","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"How many shapes were grouped in the video ? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5341","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5345","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"2 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5341_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"2\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si5352","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5356","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"3 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5352_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"3\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5564","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5568","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"4 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5564_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"4\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5407","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide5282q0","for":"Slide5282q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5421","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide5282q0","for":"Slide5282q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5435","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5282q0","for":"Slide5282q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5360","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5282q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5373","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5282q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5386","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5282q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5282","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1702","si5292","si5319","si5326","si5345","si5356","si5568","si5407","si5421","si5435","si5386"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5282"},"question":{"interactionId":"5306","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"How many shapes were grouped in the video ?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si5582","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5572q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5693","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5689","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5609","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True/False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5616","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The image added was moved to the bottom layer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5631","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5635","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5631_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5642","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5642_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5697","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide5572q1","for":"Slide5572q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5711","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide5572q1","for":"Slide5572q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5725","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5572q1","for":"Slide5572q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5650","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5572q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5663","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5572q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5676","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5572q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5572","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1702","si5582","si5609","si5616","si5635","si5646","si5697","si5711","si5725","si5676"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5572"},"question":{"interactionId":"5596","quizId":377,"title":"True/False","text":"The image added was moved to the bottom layer\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si5749","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5739q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5860","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5856","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5776","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5783","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Which of the following was demonstrated in the video ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5798","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5802","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Changing font size ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5798_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Changing font size\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5809","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5813","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Masking ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5809_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Masking\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si5913","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5917","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Converting to path ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5913_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Converting to path\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si5864","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide5739q2","for":"Slide5739q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5878","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide5739q2","for":"Slide5739q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide5739q2","for":"Slide5739q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5817","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5739q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5739q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5843","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide5739q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5739","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1702","si5749","si5776","si5783","si5802","si5813","si5917","si5864","si5878","si5892","si5843"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5739"},"question":{"interactionId":"5763","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Which of the following was demonstrated in the video\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si5459","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5481","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5489","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5497","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5505","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5513","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5521","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5470","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5477","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5485","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Maximum Score: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5493","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5501","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Attempts: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5525","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si5529","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si5543","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5449","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5449"}}},{"id":"Pool421","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":421,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Grouping Quiz","class":"project","title":"Grouping Quiz","children":["Slide5182","Slide5227","Slide5281","Slide5245","Slide5282","Slide5572","Slide5739","Slide5449"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":377,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide5282q0","Slide5572q1","Slide5739q2"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":30,"passScore":24}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5182","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide5227","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide5281","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide5245","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide5282","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide5572","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide5739","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide5449","title":"Slide 8"}]}